Dad.
Jealous, huh?
If you got to choose all over again,
with Mom and Dad protecting you
and living without a care,
you'd cherish it, right?
You'd really give me everything you have?
My illness can't be cured.
It'd be a waste not to give them to you.
Don't worry.
I'll definitely cherish
everything you leave me.
Come on, eat.
Aren't you hungry?
Thank you, Jiang Lai.
Jiang Lai.
I will definitely cherish
the life you gave me.
Wait.
Who are you?
I'm...
Liu Xia.
So it was you.
Miss Jiang Lai.
Sorry, Mr. Sheng told me to eat it.
Jiang Lai...
I just brought a fake spoon.
Just to have a meal at your place.
No need to be so mad, right?
Get out.
From now on,
don't let me see you two
anywhere near my home.
I heard
when speaking to the cops,
you said nothing good about Liu Dazhuang.
Are you really that heartless?
When Liu Xia was alive,
he didn't give a damn.
Now she's dead, he suddenly feels guilty.
He doesn't deserve any sympathy.
Liu Xia was my best friend.
I know she wouldn't want me to go soft.
I'm not a Bleeding heart like Lin Siqi.
In my book,
in life,
it should be An eye for an eye.
But to me,
you're trying to kill two birds with one stone.
First, you use Liu Xia's death
to incite Liu Dazhuang to go after Lin Siqi.
If it works,
you not only get rid of
the obstacle to marrying into the Sheng family,
you also smoothly remove
Liu Dazhuang, that Thorn in the side.
After all,
he's your real father, after all.
And the only one who might expose you.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You've got quite an imagination.
You know exactly what I mean.
I don't care about the Liu Xia and Jiang Lai stuff.
But
if you mess with Lin Siqi again,
don't blame me for getting ruthless.
Lin Siqi already
made you such a huge cuckold,
yet you still defend her at every turn.
Didn't expect
you to be such a Sentimental fool.
Zhang Xiaobei.
Since you won't take the way out I gave you,
don't blame me for being ruthless.
After all, you're not the only one
who can see through secrets.
And here's a friendly reminder:
you'd better keep some things safe.
Where the hell did it go?
And Jiang Lai...
Why did she call me Zhang Xiaobei?
Could it be...
You can go now.
Work hard next month.
I'll double your pay.
Th-thank you, Young Master.
Have a seat.
Being a servant for your family is great.
Getting paid from both sides.
But if your father finds out
you're dealing so gently with
someone who betrayed you,
he'll blow his top again, won't he?
When did you find out
I had the Key of Fate?
I heard Sheng Yuanzhou ran through a storm
just to rush home for dinner,
wolfing it down
without caring about his image.
That made me suspicious.
Plus, you tried to clear Zhang Xiaoyu's name,
and you overreacted to that text.
That pretty much confirmed it.
So you've been plotting in the Sheng family for a while.
Just basic homework.
After all, I've wanted to marry you for ages.
Taking my Key of Fate
won't do you any good.
Because I always planned
that when the time came,
I'd return to my original identity.
But if the time hasn't come yet,
and Sheng Yuanzhou...
No.
If Sheng Shizhong finds out you're a fake son,
what do you think will happen?
Who'd believe something that crazy?
Seems you don't know much about
the Key of Fate after all.
If you use someone else's Key of Fate,
it restores
the memories that person used the Key of Fate
to tamper with.
Which means...
I used your Key of Fate to have a meal.
Now I remember everything.
You're Zhang Xiaobei.
What do you want?
But you don't need to be afraid.
I have no intention of exposing you.
Then what do you want?
I want to...
be your wife.
You must be completely insane.
Then let's test it out.
And see who ends up crazy in the end.
Miss Jiang Lai isn't home.
It's fine. I'll just wait in her room.
No, no.
When Miss Jiang Lai isn't here,
no one is allowed in her room.
Even when I clean,
I have to do it when she's out.
Why don't you wait for her downstairs?
Jiang Lai is so on guard...
She must be hiding something in her room.
Fine.
Then I'll wait for her in the dining room.
This way, then.
I'll make you a cup of tea.
Okay.
My stomach suddenly hurts a bit.
The restroom is this way. I'll take you.
No need. Isn't it right there?
I know where it is. I'll go myself.
While I'm in the bathroom,
can you make me a cup of...
Lemon, ginger, lavender,
and honey Pu-erh tea?
The lemon has to be juiced.
The ginger has to be minced.
Three grams of lavender.
Pu-erh, the second steep after boiling.
Only half a teaspoon of honey.
Got it?
Got it.
Don't mess up a single detail.
I'll be able to tell.
Go on.
Didn't think you'd be this impatient.
Is it ready?
It's ready.
You're such a pain.
You said you were treating me to dinner,
to talk about Lin Siqi,
but after all this time,
you've had me posing and acting for photos.
What are you really up to?
You really can't change
your Young Master temper, can you?
These Chenpi Short Ribs are pretty good.
It's just that the chenpi is ten years old.
If it were 20 years old,
it'd taste even better.
Well, aren't you suffering.
Zhang Xiaobei...
How could I say something like that?
Such picky taste.
So what about Lin Siqi did you want to tell me?
Nothing.
I just wanted to remind you
to treat my best friend right.
She truly loves Zhang Xiaobei.
What do you mean?
I'm warning you.
If I catch you again
doing anything that breaks trust,
it won't be as simple as making Sheng Yuanzhou
pose with a spoon for a staged photo.
After all, I just want to be Sheng Yuanzhou's wife.
Whoever Sheng Yuanzhou is,
I don't care.
Dad.
There's nothing to eat at home.
Can you give me some money?
Dad!
What?
I'm hungry.
Go away. Don't bother me.
Asking for money now?
What money?
I have no money to give you.
I can't even feed myself.
What's wrong?
Jealous?
Guess you're not that heartless after all.
How did you know I was here?
Don't you shop at this mall all the time?
Seems like you've been paying attention to me.
What,
you finally interested in me?
Not interested.
That's why we need to build some chemistry.
What do you mean?
Don't you want to be my wife?
Then we have to build some chemistry, right?
You're not after something else, are you?
I heard Liu Dazhuang confessed.
So I came to see you.
To comfort me?
Do you need comforting?
There's a cafe up ahead.
I'll treat you to a drink.
Let's go.
Drink it. I lost.
I don't drink sugary drinks.
I bought it just for you.
Sugar-free.
Being rich
isn't that much fun.
You just get pickier.
No sugary drinks.
No low-quality carbs.
Time's measured by the second.
Don't you feel you miss out on simple joys?
Simple joys...
I think I'm starting to understand
why Lin Siqi chose you,
instead of Sheng Yuanzhou.
Seduction doesn't work on me.
Don't forget our deal.